Guide to the Robert Pinsky Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series II. Poetry
  - Subseries: Translations
    - Dante's Inferno: drafts, typescript, holograph (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - "The Inferno of Dante," galley (title page-p. 167) c.1 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - "The Inferno of Dante," galley (pp. 169-371) c.1 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - "The Inferno of Dante," galley (title page-p. 373) c.2 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - "The Inferno of Dante," galley (Notes, pp. 375-425) (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - "The Inferno of Dante," Pinsky corrections (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - "The Inferno of Dante: A Translator's Note" (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - "The Inferno of Dante," 1994 magazine proofs (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Borris Christov (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Grand Street publications (Milosz/Pinsky) (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Czeslaw Milosz: translations by Pinsky and Hass (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Subseries: Miscellaneous Poetry
    - "Dying" (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - "The Garden" (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - "Incantation" by C. Milosz, trans. Milosz and Robert Pinsky (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - "The Landscape of the News" (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - "The Living" (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - "The Ocean Cemetery" (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - "Pinsky's Speech to His Friends" (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - "Ralegh's Prizes" (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - "Stanzas from Valéry" (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - "That Advertising has Destroyed Humanity" (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - "Three Voices" (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - "The Trials" (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - "Ungatsby at Orbach's" (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Untitled (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - "At the Falls" (Box 19a, Folder 25)
    - "At Pleasure Bay" (Box 19a, Folder 25)
    - "Barney" (Box 19a, Folder 25)
    - "Circus Music" (Box 19a, Folder 25)
    - "The Cold" (Box 19a, Folder 25)
    - "Dream" (Box 19a, Folder 26)
    - "Fairyland" (Box 19a, Folder 26)
    - "From the Childhood of Jesus" (Box 19a, Folder 26)
    - "The Garden" (Box 19a, Folder 26)
    - "The Hearts" (Box 19b, Folder 1)
    - "History of My Heart": poetry reading copy (Box 19b, Folder 2)
    - "History of My Heart": proofs and correspondence with Poetry magazine (Box 19b, Folder 3)
    - "Icicles" (Box 19b, Folder 4)
    - "Isaiah" (various titles) (Box 19b, Folder 4)
    - "Jesus and Isolt" (Box 19b, Folder 5)
    - "Lair" (Box 19b, Folder 6)
    - "Lament for the Makers" (Box 19b, Folder 6)
    - "Memoir" ("Phylacteries") (Box 19b, Folder 7)
    - "The New Saddhus" (Box 19b, Folder 8)
    - "An Old Man" (Box 19b, Folder 8)
    - "Picture" (Box 19b, Folder 8)
    - "Pilgrimage" (Box 19b, Folder 9)
    - "Prophet" ("Visions of Daniel") (Box 19b, Folder 9)
    - "Psalm 139" (Box 19b, Folder 10)
    - "Ralegh's Prizes" (Box 19b, Folder 10)
    - "The Refinery" (including unidentified postcard correspondence) (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - "The Saving" (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - "Song" (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - "Sonnet" (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - "Story" (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - "The Superb Lily" (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - "Tennis" (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - "To the Reader" (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - "The Uncreation" (various titles) (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - "Voyage to the Moon" (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - "The Want Bone" (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - "What Why When How Who" (various titles) (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - "A Woman" (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - "Avenue" (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - "The City Dark" (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - "Dreamer" (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - "Ghost Hammer" (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - "Ginza Samba" (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - "Heartmoss" (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - "House Hour" (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - "Hut" (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - "Immortal Longings" (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - "In Berkeley" (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - "Kol Nidre" (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - "A Long Branch Song" (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - "The Night Game" (various titles) (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - "Night Music" (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - "The Rhyme of Reb Nachman" (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - "Shirt" (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - "Street Music" (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - "Autobiography" (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - poetry fragments (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - "The Heart Moss" (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Glück/Pinsky Reading 12/7/93 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Series III. Criticism
  - Subseries: General
    - Articles written or collected by Pinsky re: Elizabeth Bishop (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Article on J.V. Cunningham (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Article on Robert Lowell (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Article, "Nine Good Books You May Not Have Heard Of" (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Article, "Questions in Criticism" 10/9/79 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Article, "Poetry and the World" (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Pinsky and Parkinson, "Current Unstated Assumptions About Poetry" (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - "The Answerability of the Poet" (lecture, Napa Poetry Conference, 1984) (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Bishop, Elizabeth, The Complete Poems (review) (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Contemporary Poetry and its Traditions (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Dennis, Carl, Signs and Wonders (review) (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Doggett, Frank, ed., Wallace Stevens: A Celebration, and Wallace Stevens: The Making of a Poet (review) (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Five American Poets (suggested revisions to introduction) (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Heaney, Seamus, Preoccupations (review) (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Heany, Seamus, Station Island (review) (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - The Idiom of Self: Elizabeth Bishop and Wordsworth (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Interview of Robert Pinsky, by P. Michael Campbell (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Interview of Robert Pinsky, by Adam J. Sorkin (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Poems as Jokes (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Traditions in Contemporary Poetry (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Two Responsibilities of the Poet (lecture, Napa Poetry Conference, 1984) (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Zaranke, William, The Brand-X Anthology of Poetry (review) (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Review of Seamus Heaney, Field Work (with photocopy of the text) (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - "George Oppen" (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - "T.S. Eliot: A Memoir" (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - "Control, Freedom and the Appetite for Poetry" (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - miscellaneous/unknown (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Review of Patrimony: A True Story, by Philip Roth, drafts (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Eliot, T.S. ("T.S. Eliot: A Memoir") (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Heaney, Seamus (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Freneau, Philip (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Larkin, Philip (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Lewis (Winters), Janet (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Nussbaum, Martha (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Oppen, George (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Roth, Philip (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - "Responsibilities of the Poet" (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Subseries: Reviews by Pinsky, alaphabetically by author
    - Reviews of work by: A (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Reviews of work by: B-C (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Reviews of work by: D (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Reviews of work by: E-G (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Reviews of work by: H (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Reviews of work by: K (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Reviews of work by: L (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Reviews of work by: M (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Reviews of work by: N (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Reviews of work by: O-P miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Reviews: Poetry Anthology (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Reviews of work by: Q-R (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Reviews of work by: S (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Reviews of work by: T-V (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Reviews of work by: W-Z (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Subseries: The Situation of Poetry
    - Table of Contents, Preface, and Acknowledgments (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Drafts and revisions, Chapter One (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Drafts and revisions, Chapter Two (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Drafts and revisions, Chapter Three (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Drafts and revisions, Chapter Four (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Drafts and revisions, Chapter Five (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Index and footnotes (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Notes (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Readers' comments on manuscript (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Complete draft, Chapters I--III (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Complete draft, Chapters IV--V (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Final draft, Chapters I--III (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Final draft, Chapters IV--V (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Edited manuscript, Chapters I--III (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Edited manuscript, Chapters IV--V (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Series IV. Academic Papers
  - Subseries: General
    - Notes, various dates: 2 spiral notebooks (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Notes, various dates: black notebook (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Undergraduate papers (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Undergraduate honors thesis, "The Plays of T.S. Eliot" (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Graduate papers (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Graduate thesis, "The Poetry of Walter Savage Landor" (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Class syllabi and lecture notes (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Student papers--Spring, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Student papers--Spring, 1974, Lily A. Awad (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Student Poetry (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Interviews with Pinsky (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Subseries: Trip to Eastern Europe
    Material concerning Pinsky's trip to Eastern Europe, made in March of 1981. Included are guest lists to the various dinners and ceremonies he attended, as well as invitations, itineraries, receipts and addresses of those he met on the trip.
    - Addresses, guest lists, schedules, poetry reading announcements (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Receipts (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Material concerning Pinsky's trip to Eastern Europe, made in March of 1981. Included are correspondence, vouchers, schedules, lists of contacts, host country responses to trip, participant report. (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Series V. Memorabilia
  - Invitations to readings (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Notes and memos (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Dealers' catalogs (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper articles (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous drawings and photographs (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified poetry (photocopy) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Travel memorabilia (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Announcements of poetry readings and miscellany (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Printed Ephemera (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Printed ephemera (incl. "The T.S. Eliot Centenial") (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Series VI. Poetry and Prose by Other Writers
  - A-C, misc.
    - Andrews, Bruce (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Berrigan, Ted (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Bidart, Frank (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Bidart, Frank (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Bidart, Frank (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Bidart, Frank (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Burns, Gerald (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Cain, William E. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Carnochan, Brigitte ("Interview with Janet Lewis") (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Cheuse, Alan (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Corn, Alfred (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Fagin, Larry (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - F-L, misc.
    - Farley, Jean (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Ferry, David (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Gibbins, Reginald (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Greenblatt, Steven (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Gullans, Charles (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Hellerstein, Kathryn (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Hellerstein, Kathryn (1 yellow notebook) (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Kalstone, David (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Kenner, Hugh (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Leibowitz, Herbert (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Levinger, Larry (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Lowell, Robert (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - M-R, misc.
    - McGuire, Philip C. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - McMichael, James (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - McWhorter, Diane (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Mendelson, Edward (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Mooradian, Mary Ann (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - New York Times Book Review (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Parini, Jay (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Parkinson, Thomas (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Prunty, Eugene Wyatt (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Ruby, Beth (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - S-Z, misc.
    - Sabin, Margery (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Saroyan, Aram (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Schwartz, Lloyd (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Schwartz, Lloyd (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Schwartz, Lloyd (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Thorburn, David (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Vendler, Helen (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Viereck, Peter (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - von Hallberg, Robert (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Zeldich, Bernice (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Unidentified
    - Unidentified (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - B, misc:
    - Bidart, Frank (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Bishop, Elizabeth (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Bly, Robert (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Bogen, Don (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Booth, Philip (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Bromwich, David (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - C-F, misc:
    - Cardoni, Edmund (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Clampitt, Amy (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Corey, Stephen (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Dennis, Carl (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Feldman, Irving (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Ferry, David (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Fields, Ken (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Freedman, William (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - G, misc:
    - Goldensohn, Barry (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Galassi, Jonathan (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Galvin, Brendan (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Gibbons, Reginald (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Goldbarth, Albert (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Greger, Deborah (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - H, misc:
    - Hass, Robert (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Hollander, John (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Hadas, Rachel (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Hall, Donald (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Halliday, Mark (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Halpern, Daniel (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Helfgott Hyett, Barbara (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Hughes, Ted (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - K, misc:
    - Kaufman, Janet (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Kenyon, Jane (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - L, misc:
    - LiCalsi, Lynn (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Lea, Sydney (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Leithauser, Brad (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Lewis (Winters), Janet (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Lockwood, Margo (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Logan, John (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - M-O, misc:
    - Madoff, Steven (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Mathews, Aiden Carl (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Matthews, Jack (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Matthews, William (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Mazur, Gail (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - McMichael, James (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - McPherson, Sandra (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Melone, Debbie (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Meredith, William (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Michael, Lenny (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Morgan, Frederick (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Moss, Howard (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Murpphy, Romaine (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Oliver, Ray (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - P, misc:
    - Peck, John (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Pack, Robert (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Parini, Jay (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Pastan, Linda (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Peseroff, Joyce (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Pollens, David (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - R, misc:
    - Ratuskinskaya, Irina (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Ruark, Gibbons (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Ryan, Michael (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - S, misc:
    - Sadoff, Ira (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Salter, Mary Jo (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Seiler, Barry (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Shattuck, Roger (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Shore, Jane (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - St. John, David (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Strand, Mark (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - T-Z, misc:
    - Tompkins, Elise (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Updike, John (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Wagoner, David (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Waterhouse, E (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Williamson, Alan (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Winters, Anne (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Wormter, Baron (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Yamamoto, Traise (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Zagajewski, Adam (trans. Renata Gorczynski) (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified
    - Unidentified (incl. "Robert Lowell at Frank's...", Paul [?-see also unidentified "Paul" in box 19, folder 12) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - A-Z, misc.
    - Bidart, Frank (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Hass, Robert (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - A-Z, misc.
    - Bidart, Frank: "Introduction" to Pinsky reading at 92nd St. Y (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Hall, Donald: Old and New Poems (incl. 2 letters by Hall) (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Hass, Robert: (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Hass, Robert: "Milosz at 80" (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Hass, Robert: "Fragments of Summer" (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Hass, Robert: "In the Bahamas" (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Hass, Robert: "Misery and Splendor" (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Hass, Robert: "The Novelist among the Corbets at the Louvre" (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Hass, Robert: "On Squaw Peak" (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Hass, Robert: "Quartet" (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Hass, Robert: "Squaw Valley" (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Hass, Robert: "Thin Air" (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Heaney, Seamus: Seeing Things (proofs) (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - A-Z, misc.
    - Breslin, Paul, "Vicissitudes of Orpheus" (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Bidart, Frank (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Bidart, Frank (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Bidart, Frank (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Bidart, Frank (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Ferry, David (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Heany, Seamus (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Shapiro, Alan - "The Fight, 1969" (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Sward, Robert (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - TIKKUN Supplement (ed. Pinsky; various poets) (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - TIKKUN Supplement (ed. Pinsky; various poets) (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Series VII. Galley Proofs and Oversized
  - Subseries: Oversized
    - Oversized Poetry: The Sentences (musical score) (Box 29)
  - Subseries: Galley Proofs
    - General Galleys:
      - Sadness And Happiness (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Sadness And Happiness (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Sadness And Happiness (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - An Explanation of America (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - An Explanation of America (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - An Explanation of America (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - An Explanation of America (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - The Situation of Poetry (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - The Situation of Poetry (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - The Situation of Poetry (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - The Situation of Poetry (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - The Situation of Poetry (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - History of My Heart (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - History of My Heart (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - "The Living" (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - "Mindwheel" (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - various poems for an anthology of contemporary American authors (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - various poems and other writing (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Smith Poets, Golden Gate Watershed (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - book cover designs (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - "Autobiography" (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - "Jesus and Isolt" (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Poetry and the World (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Poetry and the World (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Want Bone (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - "Dreamer" (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - "Falling Asleep" (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - "Ginza Samba" (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - "The Lenore Marshall Prize" (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - "A Love of Death" with introduction (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - "Mysteries of the Future" (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - "An Old Man" (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - "Ralegh's Prizes" (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - "Visions of Daniel" (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - "Voyage to the Moon" (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - "Want Bone" (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Dante Galleys:
      - Canto XIII (Boston Review) (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - Canto XXV (Raritan Quarterly Review) (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - Canto XXVIII (The Paris Review) (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Series VIII. Interviews
  - "A Conversation with Robert Pinsky" (Jim Knowles and Harry Thomas, Feb. 2, 1993) (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - "A State of Letters: A Conversation" with Pinsky, Saul Bellow, Seamus Heaney, Derek Walcott, Joseph Brodsky, Leslie Epstein and Christopher Ricks (Box 28, Folder 12)